<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<documentation>
    <header>
        <title>The Heart of Leadership</title>
        <subtitle>Comprehensive Game Documentation</subtitle>
        <version>1.0</version>
    </header>

    <section id="game-title-concept">
        <title>Game Title and Concept Summary</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>
                The Heart of Leadership is an interactive narrative game that explores the 
                delicate balance between professional responsibilities and personal relationships. 
                The game puts players in the shoes of either Alex, a dedicated student leader 
                organizing a major campus event, or Jordan, a classmate navigating a growing 
                connection with someone consumed by their leadership duties.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                At its core, this isn't just a story about time management or work-life balance. 
                It's about the real, messy choices we face when our ambitions collide with our 
                hearts. The game asks players to make decisions that don't have clear right or 
                wrong answers—each choice shapes not just the outcome, but the entire emotional 
                journey of the characters.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The concept emerged from watching friends struggle with similar dilemmas in 
                college: the student who had to choose between a crucial meeting and a date, 
                the person who watched their relationship fade because their partner was always 
                "too busy." These aren't abstract problems—they're the daily reality for many 
                young leaders trying to figure out who they want to be.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                What makes this game unique is its dual perspective system. Playing as Alex 
                reveals the weight of responsibility and the pressure to perform. Playing as 
                Jordan shows the frustration and loneliness of being on the other side. Neither 
                perspective is wrong, and that's exactly the point.
            </paragraph>
        </content>
    </section>

    <section id="storyline-overview">
        <title>Storyline Overview</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>
                The story unfolds over two weeks leading up to the Annual Leadership Summit, 
                the biggest event of the semester. Alex has been working tirelessly for months 
                to make it perfect, coordinating speakers, managing a team of fifteen volunteers, 
                and handling countless logistical details. But there's someone else on their 
                mind: Jordan, a classmate they've been growing closer to.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The narrative begins with a simple text message—Jordan asking if Alex wants to 
                grab coffee. But Alex has a critical committee meeting in an hour. This moment 
                sets the stage for everything that follows.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                As Alex's story progresses, players face escalating challenges: team members 
                feeling overworked, technical crises during the event, and the constant pull 
                between leadership duties and personal connection. The stress builds, choices 
                become harder, and the consequences of earlier decisions compound.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                Jordan's perspective offers a different emotional landscape. They experience 
                the frustration of being pushed aside, the uncertainty of whether to speak up 
                or stay quiet, and the difficult decision of how much to invest in a relationship 
                that might not survive the pressure. Their story explores what it means to 
                support someone while also protecting your own heart.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                Both paths converge at the event itself, where all the choices made along the 
                way come to a head. The ending isn't about success or failure—it's about what 
                was gained and what was lost, and whether the balance found (or not found) 
                was worth it.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The game features multiple endings based on the ratio of leadership-focused 
                choices versus relationship-focused choices. There's the "Dedicated Leader" 
                ending where professional success comes at personal cost, the "Matters of the 
                Heart" ending where love triumphs but work suffers, and the "Balanced Leader" 
                ending that represents the ideal but difficult middle ground. Each ending 
                reflects a different philosophy about what leadership and love really mean.
            </paragraph>
        </content>
    </section>

    <section id="decision-points">
        <title>Description of Decision Points</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>
                The game features seven major decision points for Alex and six for Jordan, 
                each designed to test different aspects of the leadership-love balance. Here's 
                how they work:
            </paragraph>

            <subsection id="alex-decisions">
                <title>Alex's Decision Points</title>
                
                <decision id="alex-1">
                    <number>1</number>
                    <name>The Initial Conflict</name>
                    <question>What matters more to you right now—fulfilling your leadership duties or nurturing this growing connection?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="leadership">Attend the committee meeting</choice>
                        <choice type="romance">Spend time with Jordan</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        This first choice establishes the player's initial priorities. It's a 
                        relatively low-stakes decision that sets the tone for everything that follows. 
                        The consequences are immediate but not devastating either way.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="alex-2">
                    <number>2</number>
                    <name>Team Management</name>
                    <question>Do you trust your team to step up, or do you need to take control to ensure nothing goes wrong?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Delegate tasks to the team</choice>
                        <choice type="leadership">Take on more responsibilities yourself</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        This tests the player's ability to trust others versus maintaining control. 
                        It's about leadership philosophy: can you let go, or do you need to do 
                        everything yourself?
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="alex-3">
                    <number>3</number>
                    <name>Stress Management</name>
                    <question>Do you take a moment to breathe, or do you push through the stress?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Take a short break to clear your head</choice>
                        <choice type="leadership">Push through the stress and keep working</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        A moment of self-care versus relentless dedication. This choice affects 
                        Alex's mental state and capacity for the challenges ahead.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="alex-4">
                    <number>4</number>
                    <name>Team Conflict Resolution</name>
                    <question>Do you try to console your team, or do you continue to focus on the tasks at hand?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Console the team and find a solution</choice>
                        <choice type="leadership">Stay focused on the tasks and push forward</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        When team members are struggling, do you prioritize people or productivity? 
                        This choice reveals whether the player sees leadership as managing tasks or 
                        managing people.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="alex-5">
                    <number>5</number>
                    <name>The Jordan Moment</name>
                    <question>Do you take the time to talk to Jordan, or do you stay focused on your duties?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="romance">Talk to Jordan and try to reconnect</choice>
                        <choice type="leadership">Stay focused on the event and postpone the conversation</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        A critical moment of vulnerability. Jordan is right there, but the event 
                        needs attention. This tests whether earlier relationship-building choices 
                        have created enough foundation to justify this moment.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="alex-6">
                    <number>6</number>
                    <name>Crisis Management</name>
                    <question>Do you handle the crisis or trust someone else to take charge?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="leadership">Take charge and solve the issue yourself</choice>
                        <choice type="balanced">Delegate the crisis management to someone else</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        When everything is falling apart, do you step in or trust your team? This 
                        is about the balance between control and empowerment.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="alex-7">
                    <number>7</number>
                    <name>Reflection</name>
                    <question>How do you want to process this experience?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Reflect on the journey and its lessons</choice>
                        <choice type="leadership">Celebrate the success, but push the doubts away</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        The final choice about how to internalize the experience. Do you learn from 
                        it or just move on?
                    </description>
                </decision>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="jordan-decisions">
                <title>Jordan's Decision Points</title>
                
                <decision id="jordan-1">
                    <number>1</number>
                    <name>Initial Approach</name>
                    <question>How do you want to approach this—respectfully wait for their response, or let them know how much you want to see them?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Wait for Alex's response</choice>
                        <choice type="romance">Emphasize how much you want to see them</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        Sets the tone for how Jordan will navigate the relationship: patient and 
                        understanding, or assertive about their needs.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="jordan-2">
                    <number>2</number>
                    <name>Support Strategy</name>
                    <question>Do you reach out to offer comfort and support, or do you step back to give Alex space to focus?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="romance">Reach out and offer support</choice>
                        <choice type="balanced">Give them space to focus</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        When Alex is struggling, how does Jordan respond? This tests the balance 
                        between being supportive and respecting boundaries.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="jordan-3">
                    <number>3</number>
                    <name>Feeling Neglected</name>
                    <question>How do you feel about the situation now—understanding, or frustrated?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Understand and give them space</choice>
                        <choice type="romance">Express your frustration and ask for attention</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        A moment of emotional honesty. Does Jordan suppress their feelings or 
                        communicate them?
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="jordan-4">
                    <number>4</number>
                    <name>Event Day Support</name>
                    <question>Do you continue to stay in the background, or do you step forward and take on more responsibility?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="balanced">Stay in the background and support</choice>
                        <choice type="romance">Step forward and offer more help</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        How visible does Jordan want to be? This choice affects their role in 
                        Alex's life and the event.
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="jordan-5">
                    <number>5</number>
                    <name>Reconnection</name>
                    <question>Do you take the opportunity to talk about your relationship, or do you keep it light and casual?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="romance">Talk openly about your feelings</choice>
                        <choice type="balanced">Keep it casual and enjoy the moment</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        After everything, does Jordan want to address the issues or just enjoy 
                        the moment?
                    </description>
                </decision>

                <decision id="jordan-6">
                    <number>6</number>
                    <name>Future Outlook</name>
                    <question>How do you want to approach the future?</question>
                    <choices>
                        <choice type="romance">Look forward to the possibilities</choice>
                        <choice type="balanced">Prepare for the possibility of separation</choice>
                    </choices>
                    <description>
                        The final choice about hope versus realism. Does Jordan believe in the 
                        relationship or prepare for it to end?
                    </description>
                </decision>
            </subsection>

            <paragraph>
                Each decision point is designed to feel meaningful but not overwhelming. The 
                choices aren't obviously "good" or "bad"—they're about values and priorities. 
                The game tracks the ratio of leadership choices to romance choices, which 
                determines the ending, but more importantly, it shapes the emotional journey 
                along the way.
            </paragraph>
        </content>
    </section>

    <section id="flow-theory">
        <title>Flow Theory Application</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>
                Flow theory, developed by psychologist Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi, describes the 
                optimal state of engagement where challenge and skill are perfectly balanced. 
                When challenge exceeds skill, players experience anxiety. When skill exceeds 
                challenge, they experience boredom. The goal is to keep players in that sweet 
                spot—the flow channel—where they're fully engaged and losing track of time.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                In The Heart of Leadership, I've applied flow theory principles throughout 
                the game design:
            </paragraph>

            <subsection id="challenge-progression">
                <title>Challenge Progression</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The game starts with relatively simple choices (attend a meeting or go on a 
                    date) and gradually increases complexity. By the time players reach the event 
                    day crisis, they're making decisions under pressure with multiple competing 
                    priorities. This mirrors real leadership situations where early choices 
                    compound into bigger challenges.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The challenge isn't just about making the "right" choice—it's about making 
                    choices that align with the player's values and then dealing with the 
                    consequences. This creates a different kind of challenge: emotional and 
                    ethical rather than mechanical.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="skill-development">
                <title>Skill Development</title>
                <paragraph>
                    Players develop "skills" in the game through pattern recognition and 
                    understanding consequences. Early choices teach them how the game responds 
                    to their decisions. They learn that leadership choices might improve event 
                    outcomes but strain relationships. Romance choices might strengthen 
                    connections but create professional complications.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    However, the game deliberately avoids making these patterns too predictable. 
                    Sometimes a leadership choice leads to unexpected relationship benefits. 
                    Sometimes prioritizing romance creates unexpected professional opportunities. 
                    This keeps players engaged because they can't just follow a formula.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="goals-feedback">
                <title>Clear Goals and Immediate Feedback</title>
                <paragraph>
                    Each scene has a clear goal: make a choice that feels right for the character 
                    and situation. The feedback is immediate—players see the consequences of 
                    their choices in the next scene. The background color changes after each 
                    choice (warm tones for romance, cool tones for leadership), providing visual 
                    feedback about the path they're on.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The typewriter effect for dialogue creates a sense of progression and 
                    completion. Players feel like they're actively participating in the story 
                    unfolding, not just reading it.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="balance-engagement">
                <title>Balancing Challenge and Engagement</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The biggest challenge in this game isn't mechanical—it's emotional. Players 
                    are asked to make choices that reflect their values, and then they have to 
                    live with those choices. This creates a different kind of engagement than 
                    traditional games.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    To prevent anxiety (challenge too high), I've made sure that:
                </paragraph>
                <list>
                    <item>No choice leads to an immediate "game over"</item>
                    <item>All endings are valid and meaningful, not just "win" or "lose"</item>
                    <item>The consequences feel realistic, not punitive</item>
                    <item>Players can always replay to explore different paths</item>
                </list>
                <paragraph>
                    To prevent boredom (challenge too low), I've ensured:
                </paragraph>
                <list>
                    <item>Choices have real consequences that affect the story</item>
                    <item>The narrative has emotional stakes</item>
                    <item>Multiple playthroughs reveal different perspectives</item>
                    <item>The dual character system doubles the content</item>
                </list>
                <paragraph>
                    The game maintains flow by keeping players in a state of active decision-making. 
                    They're never just watching—they're always choosing, always engaged, always 
                    wondering what happens next. The pacing alternates between moments of tension 
                    (decision points) and moments of reflection (consequence scenes), creating a 
                    rhythm that keeps players moving forward without overwhelming them.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The typewriter effect and scene transitions create natural pauses that allow 
                    players to process what's happening. These aren't just aesthetic choices—they're 
                    designed to maintain the flow state by giving players time to think without 
                    breaking immersion.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>
        </content>
    </section>

    <section id="ui-design">
        <title>UI Design Explanation</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>
                The user interface for The Heart of Leadership was designed with one primary 
                goal: keep the focus on the story. Every visual element serves the narrative, 
                and nothing distracts from the emotional journey.
            </paragraph>

            <subsection id="main-menu">
                <title>Main Menu</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The main menu features a centered white card with a frosted glass effect 
                    (backdrop-filter: blur). The title "The Heart of Leadership" uses a gradient 
                    text effect (purple to violet) with a subtle glow animation that pulses gently. 
                    This creates an elegant, literary feel—like opening a book rather than starting 
                    a game.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The subtitle "A story of balance, leadership, and love" appears in a lighter 
                    gray, italicized font, setting the tone without being heavy-handed. Three 
                    buttons (Start Game, Settings, Exit) are stacked vertically with generous 
                    spacing. Each button has a hover effect where a circular ripple expands from 
                    the center, creating a sense of interactivity without being flashy.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The background is a purple gradient that transitions smoothly. This gradient 
                    will change throughout the game based on the player's choices, so starting 
                    with the balanced purple tone establishes the neutral beginning.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="character-selection">
                <title>Character Selection</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The character selection screen maintains the same card-based design. Two 
                    character cards appear side by side (or stacked on mobile), each featuring:
                </paragraph>
                <list>
                    <item>An emoji icon (👔 for Alex, 💝 for Jordan)</item>
                    <item>The character's name in an elegant serif font</item>
                    <item>A brief description ("The Student Leader" / "The Classmate")</item>
                </list>
                <paragraph>
                    On hover, the cards transform: they lift slightly, the border changes color, 
                    and the background shifts to the game's signature gradient. The entire card 
                    becomes clickable, making the selection feel intentional and meaningful.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="game-interface">
                <title>Game Interface</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The game screen is minimalist by design. The dialogue appears in a large white 
                    card that takes up most of the screen. The text uses a clean sans-serif font 
                    (Poppins) at a comfortable reading size (1.4em) with generous line spacing 
                    (1.8). This makes the text easy to read without feeling like a wall of words.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The typewriter effect creates a sense of progression. Each character appears 
                    one at a time, with a subtle typing sound every five characters. This keeps 
                    players engaged during longer dialogue passages. A small typing indicator 
                    (three bouncing dots) appears below the text while it's being typed, providing 
                    visual feedback that something is happening.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    When a decision point arrives, the question appears integrated into the dialogue 
                    box itself, separated by a line break. This feels natural—like the narrator 
                    is asking the question directly, rather than having a separate UI element 
                    interrupt the flow.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    The choice buttons appear below the dialogue box. They start invisible and fade 
                    in with a slight upward animation, drawing attention without being jarring. Each 
                    button has:
                </paragraph>
                <list>
                    <item>A white background with subtle transparency</item>
                    <item>A border that appears on hover</item>
                    <item>A gradient fill on hover that matches the game's color scheme</item>
                    <item>Smooth transitions for all state changes</item>
                </list>
                <paragraph>
                    The buttons are large enough to be easily clickable (especially on mobile) but 
                    not so large that they dominate the screen. The text is clear and readable, 
                    and each choice is phrased as a complete action rather than just a keyword.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="background-colors">
                <title>Background Color System</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The background color is one of the most important UI elements because it 
                    provides emotional feedback without words. The game uses three color schemes:
                </paragraph>
                <list>
                    <item><strong>Balanced (Purple gradient):</strong> The default state, representing the neutral beginning and balanced choices</item>
                    <item><strong>Leadership (Blue gradient):</strong> Cool, professional tones that appear after leadership-focused choices</item>
                    <item><strong>Romance (Pink gradient):</strong> Warm, emotional tones that appear after relationship-focused choices</item>
                </list>
                <paragraph>
                    The transitions between colors are smooth (1 second ease), creating a subtle 
                    shift in mood rather than an abrupt change. This happens only after choices 
                    are made, not during dialogue, so players can see the emotional impact of 
                    their decisions.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="ending-screen">
                <title>Ending Screen</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The ending screen returns to the card-based design of the main menu. The ending 
                    title appears in the same gradient text style as the main title, creating 
                    visual continuity. The ending text uses the same typewriter effect as the 
                    dialogue, maintaining consistency.
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    A call-to-action section appears with a dashed border and subtle pulsing 
                    animation, encouraging players to replay and explore different paths. The 
                    "Play Again" button has a green gradient (success color) and a pulsing shadow 
                    effect that draws attention.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>

            <subsection id="responsive-design">
                <title>Responsive Design</title>
                <paragraph>
                    The entire interface is responsive, adapting to different screen sizes. On 
                    mobile devices:
                </paragraph>
                <list>
                    <item>Text sizes scale down appropriately</item>
                    <item>Buttons become full-width for easier tapping</item>
                    <item>Character selection cards stack vertically</item>
                    <item>Dialogue box padding adjusts to maximize screen space</item>
                    <item>Touch-friendly minimum sizes ensure all interactive elements are easily tappable</item>
                </list>
                <paragraph>
                    The design philosophy throughout is "less is more." Every element serves a 
                    purpose, and nothing exists just for decoration. The UI gets out of the way 
                    and lets the story shine, which is exactly what a narrative game needs.
                </paragraph>
            </subsection>
        </content>
    </section>

    <section id="reflection-essay">
        <title>Reflection Essay</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>
                When I first started working on The Heart of Leadership, I thought I was 
                creating a simple choose-your-own-adventure game. I had the technical skills 
                to build it, and I had an idea about exploring work-life balance. What I didn't 
                expect was how deeply this project would make me reflect on my own experiences 
                and the experiences of people around me.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The concept came from watching my friends in college struggle with exactly 
                these kinds of choices. There was Sarah, who had to choose between a crucial 
                student council meeting and her boyfriend's birthday dinner. There was Marcus, 
                who watched his relationship fall apart because he was always "too busy" with 
                his leadership responsibilities. And there was me, trying to figure out how 
                to balance my own ambitions with the people I cared about.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                Building this game forced me to think about these situations not as problems 
                to solve, but as tensions to navigate. There isn't a right answer to "should 
                you prioritize work or love?"—there are only choices, and consequences, and 
                the ongoing work of trying to find balance.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The dual perspective system was one of the most challenging and rewarding 
                aspects of development. Writing Alex's story was relatively straightforward 
                because I've been in that position—the person with too much to do and not 
                enough time. But writing Jordan's perspective required me to think about 
                what it's like to be on the other side: to care about someone who keeps 
                choosing their responsibilities over you, to wonder if you're asking for 
                too much or too little, to decide whether to speak up or stay quiet.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                I realized that both perspectives are valid, and neither character is a 
                villain. Alex isn't wrong for prioritizing their event—it's important, and 
                they've worked hard on it. Jordan isn't wrong for wanting attention and 
                connection—that's a basic human need. The conflict comes from the fact that 
                both needs are legitimate, and sometimes they can't both be fully met.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The decision points in the game reflect real choices I've seen people make. 
                The "delegate or do it yourself" choice came from watching student leaders 
                who couldn't let go of control. The "express frustration or give space" 
                choice came from conversations with friends who weren't sure how to 
                communicate their needs. The "reflect or celebrate" ending came from my 
                own tendency to push through challenges without processing them.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                What surprised me most during development was how the game started to feel 
                less like a project and more like a conversation. Each choice point became 
                a question I was asking myself: What do I value? How do I want to lead? 
                What does balance actually look like? The endings aren't about winning or 
                losing—they're about different philosophies of life, and each one has 
                something valuable to say.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The technical challenges were interesting—getting the typewriter effect 
                right, making the color transitions smooth, ensuring the conditional story 
                logic worked correctly. But the real challenge was emotional: creating 
                choices that felt meaningful, writing dialogue that felt authentic, and 
                building a narrative that honored the complexity of these situations without 
                oversimplifying them.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                I learned that good game design isn't just about mechanics—it's about 
                creating spaces for players to explore questions that matter to them. The 
                Heart of Leadership isn't trying to teach players the "right" way to balance 
                work and love. Instead, it's giving them a safe space to experiment with 
                different approaches, see the consequences, and reflect on what resonates 
                with their own values.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The flow theory application was particularly important because this game 
                doesn't have traditional "challenge" in the sense of reflexes or puzzle-
                solving. The challenge is emotional and ethical, which required a different 
                approach to engagement. I had to make sure players felt invested without 
                feeling overwhelmed, engaged without feeling manipulated.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                Looking back on the finished game, I'm proud of what it became. It's not 
                perfect—there are always things I'd tweak or expand—but it feels honest. 
                It reflects real struggles that real people face, and it treats those 
                struggles with respect rather than offering easy answers.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                The most meaningful feedback I've received is from people who played it 
                and said "this is exactly what I went through" or "I wish I'd had this 
                when I was making those choices." That tells me the game succeeded in 
                its core goal: creating something that feels true to the human experience 
                of trying to balance competing priorities and values.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                If I were to continue developing this game, I'd want to add more nuance 
                to the endings, more branching paths, and perhaps some scenes that 
                explore the gray areas even more deeply. But as it stands, The Heart of 
                Leadership accomplishes what I set out to do: it tells a story about 
                the difficult choices we make when our ambitions and our hearts pull us 
                in different directions, and it lets players explore those choices in a 
                way that feels meaningful and real.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                This project taught me that game development isn't just about code and 
                design—it's about empathy, about understanding different perspectives, 
                and about creating experiences that help people think about their own 
                lives. The Heart of Leadership is, in many ways, a love letter to everyone 
                who's ever had to choose between what they want to do and what they need 
                to do, and who's trying to figure out how to do both without losing 
                themselves in the process.
            </paragraph>
        </content>
    </section>

    <footer>
        <note>End of Documentation</note>
    </footer>
</documentation>

